Ondrej Valla

63B Hardinge Road, Ashford, Kent, TN24 8HB
Phone: 0785 483 1620 Email: ondrej.valla@gmail.com

Date of birthLanguagesNationalityMarital StatusDriving License20/09/1989English, SlovakSlovakMarriedFull UK

Personal Profile

I always enjoy meeting new challenges and value personal growth.

In the past ten years I have worked for different types of businesses. From manufactories to hospitality and B2C sales. In these roles I have learned how to work as a part of the team same as an individual, following the highest standards to deliver top quality service for clients.

Now after three years of working at Premier Foods as a Technical operator, I am looking for a new challenge and a new experience.

Employment History

October 2016 – Present Premier Foods, Ashford, Kent

Technical Operator

- Paxo Stuffing producing Stuffing batches for production lines
- First Aider
- Quality Champion
- SAP, Olympus
- Pedestrian power truck and Reach truck

May 2016 - October 2016 Mann Countrywide, Willesborough, Ashford, Kent

Sales Negotiator

- Working as an Estate agent, matching right properties to right buyers.
- Registering new applicants, upselling additional company service packages.
- Organising and carrying out property viewings.
- Sell progressing

December 2014 - April 2016 Zenith Staybrite, Ashford, Kent.

<u>Assistant Manager / Sales Representative</u>

- Direct Sales in a demanding customer focused environment.
- Successfully assisting Manager to lead, train and support a team of 5 to 10 people, generating over £1,000 000 worth of business per year.
- Administration & processing of new orders.
- Updating sales figures, report building and analysing progress.
- Measuring & designing quotes to specific customer requirements.
- Selling Finance packages (FCA compliance).

Holiday Inn, Intercontinental Hotel Group, Ashford, Kent

Assistant Manager (Food & Beverage) / Duty Manager / Receptionist

- Leading a team of 7 to 10 people across two departments.
 (100 guest rooms, 4 function rooms, 1 restaurant, 2 bars, 200 breakfast & 60 dinner covers) □
 Continuously reaching targets of above 80% of customer satisfaction.
- Coordinating Conferences, Weddings, Parties and other Special Events up to 200 delegates.
- Organising briefings and meetings for operation team members.
- Responsible for staff rota / time sheets.

July 2010 - April 2011
HR Go Recruitment, Premier Foods, Ashford, Kent
Temporary Grade 7 Operator

- Part of the team on lines 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 11, P, C.
- Working in health and safety manner.

Education / Training

OAL Level 2 Diploma in Food and Drink Operations *May 2019*

First Aid Course

Emergency First Aid at Work August 2017

Zenith Staybrite - four-day sales and enterprise training *December 2014*

Level 2 NVQ Diploma in Hospitality Services, Sussex Downs College

March 2012 - March 2013

ESOL Level 3, K-College, Ashford, Kent

University of Cambridge ESOL April 2011 – January 2012

Business College, Hlohovec, Slovakia

3 x A Level

The college's focus was on the retail market.

September 2005 - September 2009

Interests

Having already lived in the UK for ten years, I enjoy learning new skills by accepting new challenges, improving my English language through work, socialising, literature and films. I like exploring different cultures and their traditional cuisines by traveling and photography.